I was expecting to see, you know, like,
as always, some of the brothers have a good time.
Walk into the ZBT house and the first thing you hear
is like boom boom boom. You hear that music.
And my heart beats through music, I can't lie.
I'm an Orthodox Jew, so I keep Shabbat, I keep kosher.
And Judaism is kind of part of my everyday life.
Shabbat starts at sundown on Friday,
so I get dressed up for dinner.
I go over to Chabad, help set up. We have dinner,
then I head back home, sleep, wake up in the morning—
and go to services.
We have a beautiful meal filled with
over 100 Jewish students on campus.
Right across the street from our friends over at ZBT.
So Max and I have this friend named Rand.
My name is Rand. And he's an amazing guy.
But unfortunately, he's been stricken with tough times recently.
So we want to go console him on a Saturday afternoon.
It's like maybe 1 or 2 p.m. We're a little bored.
It's Shabbat. We don't have our phones.
So we're looking for something to do.
We decide, hey, let's go see Randy.
There was some event going on, but I wasn't really sure.
I was a little hesitant, but not really.
Basically, we kind of walked up
to the front door of the ZBT house.
Trying to see Rand, just calm him down
from whatever kind of trauma he has.
And then some person ran out in a bikini from the side,
and seemed to know Max, was like, "Hey, guys, come on over."
We see this other friend, Sophia, and she says,
"Max, Benjamin, you guys, come around the back."
And I'm like, "Okay, you know, Sophia,
she's a great girl. We trust her."
I noticed afterwards, apparently, it's not normal
for guys to just walk into a frat party.
They're usually pretty fine.
A couple pointing fingers. I don't judge.
They don't charge us, we don't charge them. That works.
There were groups of people that you could see pointing at us.
We are Jewish — but at an event like this—
Everyone's wearing wildly different clothing,
and I just saw these two guys staring up at me.
We came to support a friend. And we ended up having,
for us at least, a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
We laughed with more friends than we came with,
and that's always a good thing.
When the ZBT guys saw me,
they welcomed me with open arms.
Did anything make you uncomfortable?
No. I mean, yeah.